(Leonard:)No, no-no-no, I'm ready!
(Leonard:)I gave up the gift of
sight for you.
(Leonard:)If that's not moving on,
what is?
(Priya:)You need to cut the cord
with Penny.
(Leonard:)Oh... okay.
(Priya:)You don't sound very confident.
(Leonard:)No, no, I'm confident.
Its not like I'm unfamiliar with
the "get lost" conversation.
(Leonard:)Although, this will be the first
time I'll be the one saying it.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Priya:)I appreciate it.
(Priya:)Sure.
(Leonard:)Oh, God, you
smell so good.
(Leonard:)Of course, that
could just be
(Leonard:)my other senses
getting stronger.
(Leonard:)Hypothetically, if I had access
(Leonard:)to a Lieutenant Uhura uniform,
would you wear it?
(Priya:)Leonard, it is a source
of great pain
(Priya:)to me and my family
(Priya:)that my brother has that outfit
in his wardrobe.
(Priya:)Can we not discuss it?
I'm sorry. Never mind.
(Howard:)And was your card the jack
of diamonds?